I will say working around that many
kids, man, did make me realize that I
would hate to be in a public place and
lose a kid named Marco.
[laughter]
I know I look like a series of white
dudes.
It's like a Jim Carrey and Ryan Reynolds
gave birth to Johnny BRAVO
and Jimmy Neutron was a midwife.
I came out here and y'all were looking
at me like Vanilla Ice is making this
comeback.
>> I knew you got tattoos, but oh my
goodness.
It's good to be here, man. I'm
originally from a hooded little town in
Northern California, which is actually
inside the 707 area code. That's why I
have this tattoo right here. Yeah. I'm
just proud to be from a hood where the
area code is also lol upside down.
That's my favorite part
cuz this is how I maintain my
gangsterhood, man. Cuz if the stuff pops
off, I'M LIKE, "WHAT'S 707 TILL I DIE,
SON?" But they got like a gun or a
knife. I'm like, "OMG, JK, lol.
Stop it."
I like growing up where I grew up, man.
I appreciated growing up in the hood
because hood kids are some of the most
honest people on the planet, man.
Brutally honest. because of a hood kid.
I used to think this watch was nice.
[laughter] Then this little hood girl
came up to me one day like, "Why is your
watch made out of wood?" [laughter]
And I told her, "Well, that's what gives
it a clean look. It's actually fancy
because it's made out of wood." She was
like, "How come my mama don't have a
wooden wedding ring then?"
First of all, I don't like your tone.
And second of all, girl, get off my back
about it. I'M TRYING TO SAVE THE PLANET.
THIS WATCH IS ECO-FRIENDLY. And she was
like, I don't know who Eco is, but he
sold you an ugly watch. [laughter]
Bunch of babies kids, man.
The layout of our hood was weird, too.
Right across the street from the hood
was the county fairgrounds for the town,
which was at least cool when the fair
was in town, cuz then if you got robbed
in the hood, you could go to the fair
and try and win your stuff back
[laughter]
from some of the most ghetto carnival
barkers of all time. WHAT'S UP, GIRL?
You're looking good today. Step right
up. Today's game, we're going to guess
your pin number. Let's do this.
>> Come on down. You can win a brand NEW
YOUR WATCH. COME ON NOW. Now
you know what's fancy? It's made of
wood.
Yeah. I had all the jobs working back in
the hood, man. When I was young, I
worked in retail. Anybody ever worked
retail before?
That was about the right reaction.
[laughter]
I worked at Target, man. Nothing against
Target. It was cool, but they want to
crossrain you in every department. So,
you were useful at Target. Okay. So, I
wasn't just a cashier. I was in guest
services. I was a cart attendant. I was
in the gardening center for like a day.
That was cuz I don't know nothing about
gardening. So, I was just lying to
people all day long. [laughter]
This old lady came up to me with this
plant like, "How do you take care of
this plant? Water it.
And if it starts to die, water it less."
There's a middle ground where you
operate in there somewhere. [laughter]
Electronics was the department I got
fired in though. Man, I know less about
electronics than I do about gardening.
Guy came up to me with a camera. Hey,
how you work this camera? [snorts] Water
it. [laughter]
And if it starts to die, water it less.
So, I got fired, y'all. [clears throat]
And then I got a job at the amusement
park in my hometown. We did have an
amusement park. It was right next to the
fair and the hood. Uh, I was in the
costume department. I was a part of the
Ghetto Hero League. That was my job.
Just a bunch of hood kids and superhero
costumes. That's all it ended up being.
We had a cholo cyborg.
We called him cyorehe.
[laughter]
And we had a weird Batman. The guy who
was playing Batman didn't even like
Batman. And so I confronted him about it
one day. I'm like, "Hey homie, you don't
like Batman. Why'd you take this job?"
And he was like, "I always wanted a
butler."
[laughter]
Like, "Bro, we don't even get dental.
Someone lied to you."
I was the Green Lantern because look at
my head. [laughter]
I got a Green Lantern head. And it was
an easy job, man. All you DO IS JUST
TAKE PICTURES WITH THE KIDS. And if I
wasn't doing that, I was backstage
watching Space Jam. It was an easy job,
man. That is well within my limitations
of what I'm capable of doing. I like
that job. But one day, I was working and
some stuff went down. Okay. They had a
Superman roller coaster and it got stuck
at the top of the loop with a bunch of
people on it. And it was a big deal,
man. The news showed up, the fire
department, the police. I'm standing
there in full costume watching this go
down like, "That's a shame." [laughter]
And sure enough, kid comes running up to
me, "Green Lantern, Green Lantern." AND
I'M LIKE, "NO. [screaming]
OH,
I'm about to ruin this child's life
right now. And he was so sincere. He was
like, "GREEN LANTERN, WHY DON'T YOU FLY
UP THERE AND SAVE those people?" And I
was like, "Kid, [snorts] I'm on break.
[laughter]
Plus, it's not Green Lantern's roller
coaster. [laughter] That's the Superman
problem. You got to find him.
I will say working around that many
kids, man, did make me realize that I
would hate to be in a public place and
lose a kid named Marco.
I wish that wasn't a true story, y'all.
One day I was on set doing my thing,
full costume. This lady COMES RUNNING
BY. MARCO, MARCO,
MARCO. And I'm watching like
[laughter]
this feels like a trick.
I don't know if she's LIKE A SECRET
SHOPPER OR SOMETHING. I DON'T WANT TO
GET FIRED AGAIN. I LIKE this job, man.
20 minutes. SHE'S JUST DOING LAPS AROUND
ME. I'm like, lady, you got to cover
some ground. Okay. Have you checked the
pool?
[laughter]
Bet you'll find some kids at that pool
that are willing to help you find your
son. [laughter]
Here, wear this polo. Don't ask why.
But now I get to do this for a living,
man. Uh, I'm a professional standup
comedian. And man, y'all are seeing my
dream come true tonight is to just
perform for you fine folks. So, thank
you so much for coming out.
>> It's true, man. And I wanted to do this
since I was a kid. When I was 8 years
old, I used to sneak out of bed at night
and watch George Carlin on TV. And my
parents told me it was too adult. Don't
worry what it is. Go to bed. They
wouldn't tell me what was happening on
the TV. So I did what any kid that wants
to know information. Their parents ain't
giving it up does. I went to my teacher
at school and I was like, "Hey, there
was a dude talking. What was he doing?"
And I'll never forget what she told me.
It was one of the most influential
things anybody has ever told me in my
entire life. She looked at me and said,
"Oh, he's a comedian. He gets paid to
tell jokes for a living. He's funny like
you.
Right. Right. And I heard that and my
wheels started turning and I was like,
"You mean I should have been GETTING
PAID THIS WHOLE TIME?
Is my check in the mail? I have been
hilarious, Miss Lady."
And so the next year we had a talent
show. My teacher was bugging me all year
long. She said, "Mom, you got to enter
the talent show. You'll do so good. You
should do stand up in the talent show."
And so when I was 10 years old, I
entered my talent show and I did standup
comedy for the first time in my life and
I won my talent show doing standup
comedy when I was 10 years old. Thank
you. [applause]
It was rigged. It was not fair.
I see there's probably a lot of parents
here, man. So y'all know you go to the
10-year-olds talent show, most of those
kids don't have talent.
And I don't know why my school hated the
parents so much. They didn't give you a
choice if you wanted to sing in the
talent show. They only approved two
songs. If you was a boy and you wanted
to sing in the talent show, you had to
sing Live Levita Loca by Ricky Martin.
And if you was a girl and you wanted to
sing in the talent show, you had to sing
What a Girl Wants by Christina Aguilera.
[laughter]
That's it. There were 40 kids in the
talent show. 38 sang. [laughter]
There was a magician and me.
Yeah. Yeah. You want to turn a room full
of functioning adults into a room full
of psychopathic serial killers? Lock
them in a theater for 3 hours while a
bunch of 10-year-olds butcher the worst
two songs from 1999.
Over
and over and over again. Living loco
what a girl wants. Living loco what a
girl wants. Liv loco what a girl wants.
Living loco what a girl wants. Living
loco what a girl wants. Living loco what
a girl wants. Living loc what a girl
wants. Here's a magician. And y'all, the
magician wasn't any good.
He messed up the trick. Peter's pants
ran off stage crying,
which I thought was hilarious.
It was way funnier than anything I was
going to say up there, but that was not
what he was going for. And then it was
back to your regular scheduled
programming. Limit Loco, what a girl
wants. Lim to be Loco, what a girl
wants. Limit Loco, what a girl wants.
Here's Miles Weber doing standup comedy.
And y'all, I got a standing ovation
before I even got on stage.
A mom from the PTA threw her bra on
stage. It was crazy.
She's like, "LET HIM HAVE IT. THIS KID'S
BOLD. HE'S GOING PLACES." [laughter]
And so I won my talent show, y'all. And
to celebrate my victory, I sang What a
Girl Wants by Christina.
>> Yeah, I was working it, y'all. I earned
that ribbon.
We got some uh we got some solid
laughers here, man. I've been listening
to y'all. We got I'm a laugh condo. This
is my thing. Okay. Like, if you are a
person that is self-conscious about your
laugh cuz you think you laugh weird,
this is a safe place. Let it out. Don't
eat your laughs. It don't taste good.
Don't do that. Don't do that. Don't eat
it. It's not good for you that way.
Okay. This is a safe space for loling. I
got it tattooed on my body for that
reason, guys. Okay, if you can't laugh
weird at the comedy show, where can you
laugh weird? Okay, so yes, let it out.
LET IT OUT. All the laughs. You got a
little snicker. That's adorable. Let
that fly. Don't hold that in. You got to
laugh like Eddie Murphy had a baby with
a seal.
Let it out. Let's go.
Or laugh like Michael Jackson. and a
witch HAD A BABY. HE LIKE, COME ON. I'M
HERE FOR IT. [laughter]
One time I was doing a show at a college
in Southern California and there was a
kid in the middle of the theater, I kid
you not, who laughed exactly like this.
[laughter]
There's no joy on his face.
I'm like, homie, is this Morris code?
Are you trying to tell me something?
[laughter]
Blink twice if you're in trouble.
That was three times. I don't know what
to do with you. [laughter]
Someone help this boy, please.
He laughed. I laughed for 45 minutes. I
didn't tell a single joke. We just
laughed at each other. [laughter] That's
the whole That was the whole show.
It was hysterical. [laughter]
And if you snort, don't you sit on that.
you will catch an ulcer. Okay?
[laughter]
Do not hold in a snort. Because here's
the thing, man. I sympathize with
anybody who snorts. It's involuntary.
NOBODY WANTS TO DO IT. NO. NOBODY'S EVER
been like, "Man, I'm having so much fun
right now. I think I'm going to sound
like a pig in front of all these
strangers."
No,
that's not how it works. And I
understand THE SCIENCE BEHIND SNORTING.
EVERY SNORT is a fart. THAT WASN'T
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S A POCKET OF AIR that gets trapped
in your diaphragm
and then your body's got to make a
decision. [laughter]
And we can't send it back there. There's
people.
We got to send it to the face. Don't
hate me now.
And that SETS OFF A CATASTROPHIC CHAIN
REACTION BECAUSE YOU DON'T SNORT ONCE.
NO, you snort 37 times.
You got to get up and remove yourself so
that way it doesn't get worse. [snorts]
Excuse me. Gang way [clears throat]
coming through. I don't even like bacon.
You got TO GET OUTSIDE BEFORE YOU PEE.
CUZ if you snort and pee, they blacklist
you from Comedy for Life.
You cannot do both.
[laughter]
See, I like when people store because I
think it reminds me of like the sound my
dog makes when he's running around like
cuz I got a dog. You got any dog people
here? Yeah. Yeah. There we go. Right on.
My kind of folks, man. Uh yeah, man. I
love my dog. We have We had a very
eccentric dog, my wife and I. Uh we have
a three-legged pug
named Taz.
That's a letter for each limb still
attached to his body. [laughter]
We're praying we never have to call him
Mr. T.
[laughter]
And people always do what you guys did
when they hear we got a three-legged
dog. They're like, "A, that's so sweet.
You guys got a rescue." And I got to be
like, "Nah, we did it.
I'm still paying for that surgery."
[laughter]
And it's a boring story, man. He had a
birth defect. His elbow growing
backwards. So, he broke his leg. We had
to snip it. But we DIDN'T KNOW HE BROKE
HIS LEG FOR LIKE THREE MONTHS because he
didn't say nothing.
We just thought he had a little swagger
to him. We didn't know. [laughter]
He's cool. He's hip. Let him be all
right.
[laughter]
But that's a boring story. I don't like
it. It's not shiverous. There's nothing
exciting about that. So, what I like to
do is I like to mess with people. Folks
ask me what happened to his leg. I give
them a different answer every single
time. Kids are the best. Oh my goodness.
I love it when kids come up. This little
boy come up to me one time. I was I had
my dog at the park. He's like, "Hey,
mister. What happened to your dog's
leg?" And I just went, "We lost it." And
I kept walking.
We were playing fetch and I threw it too
hard. What do you want from me, kid?
[laughter]
Had one guy come up to me. He's like,
"Hey, what happened to your dog's leg?"
And I was like, "The war.
VIETNAM VET [laughter]
in the sense that he went to a
Vietnamese veterinarian.
I'm going to let y'all pass that one
around for a minute.
What's been weird though recently is
people been trying to guess what
happened to his leg. That's been
unusual. I'm not ready for that. I was
walking him a couple weeks ago. guy rode
by on his bicycle. HE'S LIKE, "HEY, DID
YOUR DOG GET HIT BY A CAR?"
[laughter]
What car
is going to hit a pug? And he only loses
the front right leg.
If I hit A PUG WITH MY CAR AND THAT'S
THE END RESULT, I'M RETURNING THAT CAR.
It is not safe for me to drive.
I need something with better safety
features. Like, I don't know, man, a Hot
Wheels or a Tonka truck or something. I
can't have pugs shaking ME OFF LIKE,
"WATCH WHERE YOU GOING.
What are you thinking, man? Get your
life together."
>> People always ask if my dog gets around.
Okay. I take him off his leash. I'm
like, "Catch him. Say goodbye to those
three hours.
He's faster without the leg. Don't feel
bad for him. Now he could juke, stiff
arm, spin move. HE'S THE PERFECT MADDEN
CHARACTER. [laughter]
We had to move OUT OF OUR APARTMENT
BECAUSE of him.
>> Yeah, we used to live in an upstairs
apartment and he gets in these running
fits and want you to catch him. So, if
you live downstairs underneath us and we
live in the second story apartment, it
sounds like we're filming all the
montages from Scooby-Doo upstairs.
And so it takes me like 20 30 minutes
sometimes to catch him because he's real
quick and I and I finally catch him and
I'm like but it's too late. I hear it
pounding on my front door and I open the
door and it is my neighbor from
downstairs. And to say that she is upset
is a terrible understatement.
She is red in the face, veins popping
out of her neck, yelling at me like,
"Excuse me, COULD YOU TELL YOUR DOG TO
KEEP IT DOWN FOR JUST ONE NIGHT,
PLEASE?"
AND I JUST LOOKED AT HER AND WENT, "We
already cut off one of his legs so he'd
make less noise. [laughter]
We don't know what else you want us to
do." [laughter]
[laughter]
>> So, we had to move, y'all.
>> I love my dog, man. I love him like a
son. He's not my son. I'm not one of
those people. Don't hate [laughter] me.
Because if you raised a human being
before, you hate anybody that's like,
"My dog is my child." No, it's not. It's
not the same thing. If I got a kid, I
can't leave him at home for 8 hours with
a couple of bowls with food and water.
Like, I cut a hole in the door. He'll
figure it out.
They will take your kid away from you. I
know. I've checked.
I miss my little brother.
>> [laughter]
>> My dog scared the living daylights out
of me at the beginning of this year
though, man. I had to rush him to the
emergency vet because he ate one of his
toys, which I guess is a thing that dogs
do, man. I came out the bathroom one
day, there's half a Kong toy on the
ground. I'm like, "Hey, boy, where'd you
hide the other half?" And so he starts
throwing up and I'm like, "Okay, this is
going to be a thing for a little while."
Then he keeps throwing up. Then he
starts throwing up foam. And I'm like,
"Oo, I didn't feed him foam.
And so I did what you shouldn't do in
that situation. I googled, "Hey Google,
what's wrong with my dog?" And that's
LIKE IF YOU ASK GOOGLE, "WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU when you don't feel good?"
Google's like, "Cancer. You have all the
cancer. Have you caught it all?" Like it
was a scavenger hunt or something.
[laughter]
And sure enough, Google was like, "Your
dog is dying right now." SO I'M LIKE,
[screaming] AND I FLIPPED OUT. I threw
him in the car. I speed to the emergency
vet. We get him in there, man. They take
him back through the little door. I'm
sitting in the lobby filling out
paperwork. Now, he's been back there for
like a minute, a minute and a half tops.
The doctor comes out the same door and
says, "Tazz's dad." Now, he said Taz's
dad. What I heard,
oh yeah,
was Taz is dead.
WHICH IS A MESSED UP WAY TO TELL ME YOU
KILLED MY DOG, MAN. YOU JUST KRAMER
SLIDE IN THE LAB LIKE MY BAD, BRO. YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT it's like back there.
[laughter]
So I hear this. I proceed to start big
girl crying IMMEDIATELY
like a Canadian geese and heat.
Snot bubbles coming out of the front of
my face.
My mascara ran. I wasn't even wearing
mascara, y'all.
It materialized on the front of my face
and started to run like I won Miss
America or something.
And the ENTIRE TIME THIS SITUATION'S
going down, there's a kid sitting next
to me in the lobby. the whole time he
sees everything go down. He's like, "Did
they kill your dog?"
AND I WAS LIKE, "YEAH, KID. THEY KILLED
MY DOG.
IS YOUR DOG BACK THERE, TOO?" Now he's
crying. HE'S LIKE, "YEAH." I'M LIKE,
"THEY'RE GOING TO KILL YOUR DOG, TOO.
WE GOT TO JAILBREAK HIM, MAN. IT'S THE
ONLY SHOT WE GOT."
SO, they gave me a tranquilizer.
The dog ended up being fine. He drove me
home.
And he looked gangster with a one arm,
too. It was pretty cool. Let me get you
there, pops. [laughter]
I will say this, me and my dog do have
this in common. We have terrible ADD,
which uh is a very, you know, people
don't care. That's ADD is the one
disorder people are like, "Get over get
over it, man. Just just focus. What are
you doing?" my life. There's no sympathy
for ADD. There's no walk for a cure for
ADD,
which is a shame because it would be
such a short walk.
You can do it on your lunch break, man.
We couldn't even organize the add water.
We keep getting distracted squirrel the
whole time. [laughter] Now we'd have to
get help from OCD.
>> Yeah, those folks got their stuff
together.
I got a lot of weird stuff about me,
man. I know I said that. You know, I
grew up in the hood and I appreciate
where I grew up, man, because where I
grew up, man, we used to roast each
other all the time and I learned how to
snap back real quick and that made me a
better comedian. So, I'm very grateful
for where I grew up. But you know how
when you roasting somebody and the
person you roasting, they ain't got
nothing left to roast you about, so they
start reaching for weird stuff to try
and take you down with. And that was how
I knew I was doing good is when
everybody started reaching for weird
stuff to try and take me down with in
the hood, man. Like I knew they were at
the end of their rope if they would
start to make fun of me because my belly
button's kind of high.
Yeah. Game, set, match. This is what
you're taking me down with. How old are
we? What is happening right now? It is
up there though. Check that out. It's a
little [laughter]
um Okay. Easy. Easy.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> We were doing so good.
She screamed, "Oh my goodness, it's in
your throat.
You can do anti-smoking commercials.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S MESSED UP, MAN. I'M 6 FEET TALL. MY
BELLY BUTTON'S 510. WHAT IS HAPPENING?
Cuz it's weird. If I do a slow reveal,
there should be things by now. Like,
there's too much open real estate
available on my midriff. And then pow
pow pow, shot in the chest.
[laughter]
What's weird is that my butt's in the
middle of my back. That's the weirdest.
And I'm not going to show y'all that.
That is a different show and way more
money.
>> You guys have been absolutely fantastic.
Utah. Thank you so much for coming out.
My name is Have a good night.
>> Did any of you see my last special? A
couple of you, like six of you. So, some
of you looking at me like, "Oh, 2020
blew over his hair." Oh, no. [laughter]
If you didn't see my last special, go
home and watch it. I looked like adult
Bart Simpson. My hair was all the way
up.
But we're here now, man. We're doing it.
It's good to see you all again, man.
Since I last saw you, I started doing
some cool stuff. I started coaching
comedians on how to do standup, which is
pretty cool. And that has taught me that
opening jokes are really hard. They're
very, very difficult to write. They're
really hard to write because there's a
lot of assumptions as an audience member
that you have about us when you see us,
when you hear us. And so, it's our job
as a comedian to lean into those
assumptions or shatter them with jokes
the entire set. Okay? So, there's a few
different ways you could do that. First
type of joke you could do is something
that kind of satisfies something you're
thinking and something you didn't know
that you were thinking. Comedians
usually do look like jokes to do that.
Like for example, I know that I look
like if Deadpool and Cable had a baby
[laughter]
and that baby kind of sounded like a
ghetto muppet,
which I'm okay with because muppets make
everything better. All righty.
So, that's the first type of opening
joke that I could go with. Another type
of opening joke I could tell you is I
can tell you a situation that I was in
and that situation tells you a lot about
me without saying too much. Okay? For
example, person asked me the other day
how I was doing and I told him, "I've
watched the Spice Girl movie twice this
year."
I want you to really think about that
for a second. Think about the type of
circumstances that a 30-some year old
male would find himself in to watch 1997
Spice World, not once but twice in a
calendar year. Also, notice the
language. I did not say that I saw it
twice. I said I watched it twice. Okay?
Seeing it implies that there was a
happening already taking place that I
did nothing to stop watching it. That
means I had to go seek it out. I was on
my phone and I was like, "Hey Google,
how do I watch 1997 Spice World?" And
Google was like, "Calling a therapist
right now.
You're not okay."
And then I had to go on eBay and I had
to buy a VHS copy because DVDs were
like, "We're not doing that to people."
So I had TO BUY A VHS copy off of eBay
of the Spice Girls movie. And then I had
to buy a VCR cuz I don't own a liquor
store.
It's the only place you see one of those
operating is behind the counter. All
right. Somehow attached to a TV that
looks older than the VCR. [laughter]
And then I watch Spice World twice this
year. Not on the same day. [laughter]
You know why that's worse, right? That
means whatever bad thing happened to me
one time, it happened again. All right.
But the second time it was worse because
that time I had to REWIND IT TO WATCH IT
FIRST.
>> [applause]
>> YEAH, I had to steep myself in that
energy for 90 seconds. Like, no, this is
what I want to happen.
Come on.
You get no prizes for watching Spice
World two times in one year. But if you
watch it three times, they send you
cumin for free.
That's a World Spice Spice World joke,
and it's not the nerdiest joke you're
going to hear tonight. So, buckle up.
>> [laughter]
>> A third type of opening joke is I could
give you a hot take or a hill that I'm
willing to die on and that tells you a
lot about me as a person. For example,
I'm here to tell you with full
confidence I believe that Dirty Dancing
Havana Nights is so much better than the
original Dirty Dancing. Unless you dub
the original Dirty Dancing over Muppet
Music. That's right. [laughter]
Yeah. No one puts Muppet Baby in the
corner.
You can't cuz she's Gonzo. [laughter]
She waka waka away. These dad jokes are
just going to fall out. [laughter] I'm a
dad now. They're just going to come at
me like a werewolf movie. All right. You
can hear all the dads howling at the
moon. Oh, got your nose.
[laughter]
And that's an opening bit about opening
jokes. There you go. Right on.
Thank you. [applause]
I'll tell you a little bit more about
me. I'm also a millennial. I was born in
the 80s. makes me an elder millennial,
so you should be annoyed at me for no
good reason. Uh, [laughter] yeah, man.
It's It's rough being a millennial cuz
people give you a lot of slack for it. I
just wish the shade I would get made
sense. Like, I was in the elevator a
couple weeks ago. There's an older
gentleman in the elevator with me. I was
playing with a fidget spinner that I
have. And he leaned over to me. He's
like, "In my day, we didn't need those."
I'm like, "You may not have need them,
but you you had one, though. It was just
called a rotary phone.
[laughter]
There it is." Yep. That was the original
fidget spinner. For those of you who
don't know what a rotary phone is,
that's a phone you use if you don't want
to talk to nobody. [laughter]
I was dialing all the time growing up.
I was collecting book lights before I
could read from telemarketers. It was
wonderful. And then the guy doubled
down. He's like, "Well, my generation
doesn't have any trouble focusing like
your generation does." And I'm like,
"Yeah, man. But in our defense, you also
only had like two TV stations.
[laughter] Of course you didn't have
ADD. You barely had ads.
[laughter]
And as a millennial man, I might as well
have been raised by the TV man. I might
as well have been raised by the Tanner
family or the Winslow family. I got a
friend who drinks too much was raised by
Cheers
[laughter]
cuz everybody knew his name.
I like when like the older generation
always calls the younger generation
soft. That's the word they use a lot.
This new generation is so gosh darn
soft. They're so soft. I CAN'T STAND
THEM. THEY'RE TOO SOFT. AND I'M JUST
LIKE, this is a person who has clearly
never petted a bunny,
right?
They're so soft. Or a chinchilla. What
is wrong with you? And I'm like, homie,
you don't like soft stuff that much.
Maybe women should stop shaving their
legs. What would you do then? Get some
stubble, Leroy. GRAB A HAIRY CALF. BE A
MAN. [clears throat]
Or you got a high thread crown. Come on
now, man. We all know real men sleep on
Norwegian driftwood.
You're using Q-tips, but you got a
perfectly good screwdriver. Be a man.
That's what bullies say, though, right?
They're like, "Oh man, it's soft. You're
soft." The irony is that if you were to
take all the bullies of past
generations, bring them to today, they
couldn't take getting bullied by a
millennial or Gen Z. They couldn't take
it at all. But honestly, we probably
wouldn't even bully him back. We would
just put him in the Big Brother house,
make a reality TV show with all the
bullies.
I could hear Biff Tannon in my head
right now with all the bullies from Back
to the Future. Hello, Malfoy. It's Levio
Malfoy. [laughter]
That's an intergenerational Back to the
Future Harry Potter joke. And that is
the nerdiest joke you're going to hear
tonight. Thank [cheering] you.
[applause]
Absolutely, man. I think people are just
silly. That's why I'm a dog guy, man.
Like my last special, uh, I did a lot of
jokes about my three-legged pug, Taz, so
a lot of people got to know him, which
is pretty dope, man. And Taz, since I
did that special, he's gotten older now.
He just turned 9 years old. Yeah. He's
got a gray beard. Likes to lay around
the house a lot. And so, a couple years
ago, my wife and I were like, "Hey, man,
we should probably just like get him a
buddy. That'll keep him young, right?"
And so we got him a Chihuahua pug mix.
Yeah, man. We figured that the the pug
would like supersede the annoying of the
Chihuahua. Na nigh. That is not what
happens.
You just get a giant Chihuahua with a
tiny head. That's what you get.
[laughter]
She looks like one of those glmbbas from
the Super Mario Brothers movie. Like
[laughter]
her name is Scrappy B for Scrappy Boo.
We call her that cuz she's afraid of
everything.
Taz never met a human that he didn't
love on site. Scrappy is afraid of the
wind.
Any noise, SHE'S LIKE, "WHAT WAS THAT?"
IT WAS A CAR. THEY drive by every day.
THERE'S A BIG PERSON OVER THERE. THAT'S
A CARDBOARD cutout of John Cena. You
shouldn't be able to see him anyway.
[laughter]
Wow, man. I thought we were adopting a
buddy for Taz when we got her. I didn't
know that we were adopting Hannibal
Lectar.
You can't keep her in conventional
traps. She's wild, man. Like I I got one
of those puppy play pins to try and keep
her in. So you can put them in there. Go
about your life. Got the little gates. I
put her in there. 5 seconds flat. She's
by my foot. Like that was a fun game.
What are we going to do next?
Find Clarice apparently.
Then I got a tarp to cover the top of
the play pin with duct tape. I put her
in there 10 seconds flat. She's right
there. I'm like, "What is going on right
now?" Then I got sandbags like I'm
getting ready for a flood or war. I put
her in there. I go in the living room
and I do not hear from her or see her.
And I'm like, "Haha, [laughter] I
outsmarted the pooch." Then I went in to
the kitchen where she was. Not only has
she escaped from the play pen, she
pooped on top of it. [laughter]
And I was only mad that I didn't see how
she did it. Like I got an uncle in San
Quinton. She's trying to escape the same
way. So, [laughter]
they can help each other out, man.
She is a part of a cute household now.
Uh my wife and I just had our first
child this last year, which is dope.
[cheering and applause] Thank you. Thank
you.
Yeah, man. It's pretty cool. If you've
never had a new baby before, I'll tell
you what it's like right now. Okay.
Having a new baby, it's like this. Every
day on a scale of 1 to 10, you just get
a bunch of ones and tens.
>> [laughter]
>> two through nine take a hike. I haven't
seen those numbers for a long time.
Every day there's a bunch of tens where
you're like, "Oh my goodness, we made a
miracle. What a blessing." And then
there's a bunch of ones WHERE YOU'RE
LIKE, "HOLY, JUST GO TO SLEEP."
[laughter]
LIKE, YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE MAD RIGHT NOW?
CUZ YOU'RE TIRED. JUST GO TO SLEEP.
>> There's a lot of that every day.
>> [applause]
[applause]
>> You don't know the joy.
>> Oh man. Yeah. My son's name is Robin
with a Y because my name is Miles with a
Y. And I'm like, I'm not the only person
who's going to get misspelled at
Starbucks, Playboy. Okay. Like,
that's how we're doing it. All right,
man. And he's cool, man. He's He's dope.
But if I had to describe his demeanor to
you, it would be unimpressed with life.
Everything. Like we got a bubble gun,
you know, to surround him in bubbles.
I'm like, "Oh, he's a new baby. This is
going to turn his mind to mush." And we
surrounded him in just millions of
bubbles. And he's just looking like
[laughter]
they were better in heaven. Like,
and look, they pop. They're all gone.
Nothing lasts. Like, I'm going go inside
and chew on my foot for a little bit.
[laughter]
I showed him Blues Clues for the first
time. I thought he would be impressed by
blue blues clues. I'm like, "Hey man,
let's find all three of Blue's clues."
And he's like, "They're all three on
your arm. This show sucks. [laughter]
There are some things though that he
does that I hope stick for like his
whole life into adulthood, though. Uh
there's a few things you guys that I I I
do hope sticks. Like for example, he
calls both my wife and I mama.
[laughter] I hope that sticks till he's
an adult. Absolutely. Cuz you know, one
out of I would love to be able to
introduce and be like, "Hi, I'm Robin's
mother. Nice to meet you." [laughter]
And you know, one out of every 10 times
you're going to get one guy that's like,
"You're his father." AND IT'S LIKE, "AH,
THIS IS GOING TO BUG YOU FOR a month and
a half." Another
[laughter]
thing he does is uh when you go to
change him and you take off his pants,
he laughs uncontrollably cuz he thinks
that you're going to play peekaboo with
him. I hope that sticks for his whole
life.
Take off his pants, he loses it, man.
Like he's in the changing room at
Target. They're like, "Sir, are you okay
in there?" HE'S LIKE, "I'M NOT FINE YET.
[laughter]
These pants ARE HILARIOUS.
THEY'VE GOT BELLS ON THE BOTTOMS.
As soon as I learn how to whistle, it's
all over, man. [laughter]
It's wild. Yeah, man. Being a baby owner
is weird. [laughter]
It's very strange. Looks uncomfortable,
honestly. Like my wife and I were
watching him sleep on the baby monitor a
little while ago and he was dead asleep.
But then all of a SUDDEN
[screaming]
my wife freaked out. She's like, "Oh my
goodness, WHAT WAS THAT? SHOULD WE TAKE
HIM TO THE HOSPITAL?" LIKE, "Calm down.
He probably just had a dream about
taxes."
I remember my first dream about taxes.
It sounded exactly like that.
Or the opposite happens, right? You got
a baby losing their mind, WON'T STOP
CRYING. [screaming]
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
I'm like, "Oh no, DID I BREAK HIM? WHAT
HAPPENED?" But I don't check right away
cuz if he wakes up, this is going to
ruin my night. But if he's dead, this is
going to ruin my life. So, ARE YOU OKAY?
[screaming] OKAY, here we go.
[laughter]
And when he was brand new, my wife was
kind of upset. She came to me. She's
like, "He smiles at you more than he
smiles at me." And I'm like, that may be
true, but in your defense, new babies
are super dumb.
I'm just a series of colors and shapes
that he recognizes, man. Like, look at
my head. He thinks this is a normal
man's head. Like, he sees other guys and
he's just like, "Oh, why don't you look
like a clown?" Like, he just [laughter]
so unimpressed about everything, man.
He's a very wild kid. And I'm just like,
"Don't worry about it. Don't take it too
personally. He can't even vote yet. Wait
till he's a toddler, you know?
He just learned last week his hands are
attached to him. So, I mean, [laughter]
it's not that bad. I will say this, I'm
a different person now. You know,
there's me before baby and now there's
me after baby. I'm a different human
being. I was fortunate enough to be
around my son every day of his life for
the first six months of his life. And
that's super cool because when you're
around a baby, you lock eyes with them.
You're like, "Look at you, big strong
man holding up his head and everything.
Look at you. Look at you." And you get
excited. And you should do that with
babies. But then I left home for the
first time and I saw an adult.
[laughter]
Yeah. I went to Starbucks and locked
eyes with the barista and I was like,
"Who was a big strong barista?"
[laughter]
Look at you making coffee holding up
your head and everything.
Miles with an eye. Thank you. I
appreciate that. [laughter]
I'm different now at gyms. That's
another thing. Like I used to I used to
go to the gym and I used to be impressed
when I'd see dudes curling giant
dumbbells. I'm like, "Look at that guy.
He's so strong. Look at him curling
those dumbbells." Now I don't care. I
don't care. I'm like, "Yeah, homie. You
can curl that dumbbell, but can you
soothe it?
[laughter] Can you bounce it on your hip
for 45 minutes while it screams?" No,
you cannot, sir. [laughter]
You can lift 200 lb above your head, but
it didn't even puke on you.
>> [laughter]
>> Look at you staying dry for the duration
of your activity.
I could deadlift 400 lb. Yeah, man. But
then it didn't try and get away FROM YOU
ONE TIME.
YOU JUST GOT TO PICK IT UP AND PUT IT
BACK DOWN LIKE NOTHING WAS WRONG. IT
DIDN'T try and vader salt out of your
hands.
It didn't decide to test the structural
integrity of its spine while you were
doing a rep.
Less deadlifts, more deadlifts. I'm
impressed by those. [laughter]
But it didn't help my case when I lock
eyes with the guy across the gym and I'm
like, "WHO'S THE BIG STRONG MAN?"
And he was into it. He's like, "I am."
[laughter]
Now we're lifting partners. His name is
Hank. He's a cool guy. [laughter] I help
him with his squats.
Yeah, man. You also get a lot of baby
merch when you get a baby. That's
another thing that happens, man. They
got all the merchandise. We got a baby
wrap, which is pretty cool. It's just a
long cloth that you wrap around yourself
in 37 different ways. You jam him in
your chest and he sleeps for a month and
a half.
It's such a cool invention. And to me,
doing that is like the same thing as
like, ladies, when you get out the
shower and you do that thing to your
head with a towel where you make your
head a monument to soft serve ice cream.
And gentlemen, you could always tell
what kind of mood your lady is in when
she does that where her eyebrows rest on
her face. Like, cuz if they sit real low
and relax like a cholo, it's just like,
"Okay, that's fine." It's like, "Hey,
Holmes, let's get some snacks." Like,
but if she got them in the middle of her
head back here like Tyra Banks, it's
like, "Oh, I GUESS THE LAUNDRY IS DOING
ITS STUFF TODAY." [laughter]
LIKE, BABY, you got to loosen that up.
You got veins popping out why I don't
think they're supposed to be popping
[laughter] out.
Oh man, it's wildest. And I wanted to
teach my wife how to do the rap, you
know, cuz I was like, "Hey man, it's a
cool feeling to do the rap and then have
him tucked in there, man. Let me teach
you how to do it." She's like, "Yeah,
Miles. You know what else is a cool
feeling? Growing him and carrying him
for 9 months." [laughter] I'm sure the
rap is the exact same feeling, though.
It's your turn to carry him for 9
months. Boo boo. [laughter]
What are you going to do? Another cool
thing we got is we got a a baby monitor
with a night vision camera on it so we
could watch him sleep. Super cool
invention. I just don't like the name of
it. It's called the Super Uncle.
Right. Right. Tell me you had a creepy
uncle without telling me you had a
creepy uncle. [laughter]
I would have loved to have sat in on
that meeting when they were coming up
with that name. Like, all right, we got
a monitor. Watch as your baby sleep.
What's that remind you of? Oh, my uncle
Dale for sure.
>> [laughter]
>> He used to watch me sleep all the time
growing up and we didn't for AC so he
would just breathe on me. I miss Uncle
Tail.
>> I hope Scrappy gets him out of San
Quinton next week. [laughter]
Another thing we got is we got a white
noise machine for the baby cuz babies
like white noise cuz they're racist.
[laughter]
I wanted to get a black noise machine.
It plays Earth, Wind, and Fire.
just on LOOP
and then it turns off automatically on
the 21st night of September and that is
the last earthly empire reference
that I have. [applause]
Yeah, man. And my wife explained to me
like what it does. She apparently it
simulates the sound that babies hear
when they're in the womb and it's
supposed to calm them down, make them
fall asleep super duper quick. And I'm
like, "Oh, that's a dope. Let's get
two." Absolutely. And so we get it, we
bring it home, my wife presses play on
the white noise machine and it goes
[screaming]
and I'm like, "What was that?"
[laughter]
She's like, "That's the white noise."
I'm like, "That's the white devil noise.
That's the sound IN YOUR TUMMY." LIKE,
"DID YOU SWALLOW A BIG SCREEN TV AND
BREAK IT? WHAT HAPPENED?" LIKE, tell me
this ON A FIRST DATE. I DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE USING THE SAME BATHROOM as
you anymore. Like you swallowed the
Cloverfield monster and just let him
live in there. Like what is happening?
And why are we wasting MONEY ON THIS
DEVICE WHEN I could break a radio for
free?
Just tune it around the Telmundo
stations. Those ones never come in
clear. It always sounds like they're
spitting.
Maybe the tuba will calm him down more.
[laughter]
Let's try that, man. So, what also has
been cool has been watching all of our
friends gravitate towards him. Everybody
wants to be uncle this and auntie that.
We got one friend who claimed the name
Uncle Javi, but her real name is Amy.
[laughter]
And I like that. I'm going to allow it.
I think more white women should identify
as Spanish uncles. [laughter]
I think that would bridge the divide in
this country. It's like, nah, I'm going
over to Uncle Jav's Auntie Karen. You
call the cops too much. [laughter]
That girl was just trying to sell some
lemonade.
Uh, another cool thing is when my mom
got to meet him for the first time.
That's always cool, right? When your
grandparents get to meet the baby for
the first time. But it was weird because
I ain't never seen my mama be around a
baby since I was a baby. And she started
doing things and saying things and I was
like, "Oh, how am I still alive?"
I didn't know the gift of life I had.
SHE WAS DOING THINGS AND SAYING THINGS
YOU SHOULD NEVER DO to a baby. She was
like, "Oh, is he being fussy? Put some
whiskey on his gums.
He'll get drunk and pass out.
They're super cute when they're drunk."
[laughter]
And you can't argue with your parents
about it either, cuz they always give
you the same excuse. They're like,
"Well, you're here and you're okay." And
it's like, "Yeah, man, but I twitch a
lot.
[laughter]
This is not what I thought it was going
to be, man. Like, I had all these
predispositions about how being a father
was going to be in my head, and none of
it's been like that, man. So, just if
you're going to have kids, just suspend
all your beliefs. Even the labor and
delivery wasn't what I thought it was
going to be. I saw TV. I figured I knew
how it works, man. It was not LIKE THAT
AT ALL. WE ONLY SAW THE DOCTOR LIKE two
times the whole day. Like, he came in
first time early in the day just eating
popcorn. HE HAD SNACKS. HE'S JUST LIKE,
"HEY, WHAT'S UP you crazy kids? What do
you guys do for a living? There's a baby
in there. All right, I'm going to be in
my office playing Nintendo. Call me when
something cool happens." [laughter]
>> No, man. If you're playing Nintendo, how
you're not going to come back in here,
pull the baby out, blow on it, and put
it back in. Like,
I know how this works. And another weird
thing was one of the nurses saw my last
triar special and so she was geeking
out. She's like, "Oh my god, this is so
okay. can we get like a selfie? Is that
okay? And I'm like, yeah, just be aware
of what's in the background, but yeah,
that's fine. And so we take our selfie
and then she's looking at her phone.
She's like, oh my goodness, my friends
are going to lose their minds when they
find out I met Shane Smith. [laughter]
Yeah, it's Shane with a Y. Uh,
[laughter]
>> yeah, tag me in that when I leave the
hospital. It's going to be a surprise
for all of us.
>> [laughter]
>> And my wife is the toughest person I've
ever met in my entire life, y'all. My
wife was in labor for 21 hours and she
worked through labor between
contractions. She had her laptop open on
her lap. She was sending out emails to
clients while she was having
contractions. The nurse came in like,
"Are you working right now?" She's like,
"Check your tone, check gas prices, and
then get back to me. This kid's going to
eat." [laughter]
And then I got to help when my wife was
pushing. So my job when she was pushing
was I would roll up her leg, we'd do a
count and then I put her back down, wait
for the next contraction to come. We did
that for 3 hours. 3 hours. After 3
hours, the doctor was like, "Hey man,
not for nothing. We might have to get
the vacuum out to get this kid out." And
I was like, "What did you say [laughter]
with your face?" vacuum like like Hoover
with a bowling ball like I could have
did this at home for free is what I'm
understanding.
What's the copay on a Dirt Devil? Give
me my options
9 months ago. What are we doing playing
these games? And he's like, "Nah, man.
You don't understand. This is what we do
right before we do a C-section. So, it's
kind of serious." And I was like, "Oh,
okay. Not for nothing. Sidebar, let's
have a discussion. I know my wife better
than anybody. I got an idea." And so we
walk over to the side and meet me the
doctor and the nurse and I'm like, "Hey
man, if you can do this one thing and
commit to it, sell it like your life
depended on it. I think this is going to
ease things on. You're going to have a
baby sitting here laughing in a few
minutes." And they're like, "All right,
you know your wife better than anybody.
We'll give it a go." So we walk back to
my wife. We wait for the next
contraction to come. And when that
contraction comes, I rolled up my wife's
leg. The nurse came running from across
the room, slid next to my wife, AND
WENT, "ONE, [screaming] TWO, THREE, RING
THE BELL." My wife laughed. My son was
born.
[applause]
>> 22 years of watching professional
wrestling for the coolest moment of my
entire life.
And to celebrate, I gave the doctor the
Hulk Hogan leg drop like a real
American.
And then the doctor came up to me and
was like, "You want to cut the cord?"
And I was like, "Nah, I got a thing with
belly buttons." My name is Miles River.
Thank you so much, Ryar. I love you
guys.